Welcome to hell.
The place where I stand
is hell itself.
Scared stiff?
Or just faking composure?
Let me tell you,
everyone fears death.
I bet you've already
wet yourself.
Anna,
look at your Eastern hero.
He's nothing but a pitiful little worm.
Your Highness,
please sit back and watch.
The Prince is merely testing for you
the worth of this distinguished guest.
If he can't handle even this,
then he truly doesn't deserve your favor.
If he's easily subdued,
then he isn't worthy of my admiration.
What I hate most are the Chinese.
I purposely shot one dead a few days ago.
With this very gun.
The man you killed was my brother.
His name was Wu Qian.
What a coincidence.
Looks like today
I can send you to meet your brother.
It is fate, indeed.
But a cursed one.
The karma between us has come due.
Today, it must be settled.
Settled?
By the likes of you?
Look at that scrawny frame of yours.
Look at your pathetic, shabby state.
You, talking karma with the Black Family?
Are you worthy?
What a joke.
The funniest joke I've heard all year.
A hundred times funnier than clown shows.
Laugh while you can.
With a gentle pull of the trigger,
your head will burst like a watermelon.
Understand?
You worthless piece of trash.
Go to hell!
You're dead!
I'll tear you limb from limb!
Death won't be your end.
I'll make you feel every ounce of pain,
day and night,
year after year.
This is the punishment you deserve.
Wu Ming, what did you do to my brother?
I just crippled him,
to make him repent in agony.
He just killed a few parasites.
And you torture him like this?
You monster!
In my eyes,
he is the real monster.
I'm being merciful as it is.
You'd better heal my brother,
or the Black Family will end you.
Your entire family bloodline is here.
Notify your Marquis.
He has ten minutes to get here.
Otherwise,
your line ends today.
Yes, sir.
Wu Ming's cards still haven't changed.
That means he altered their very essence.
Tian Yi still falls a notch short.
But that was many years ago.
After all these years,
Tian Yi hasn't stayed stagnant either.
He must be at an unfathomable level now.
I'm going to the Taoist Medical Clinic.
Do you want to come with me?
You won't find Wu Ming.
What's wrong?
What on earth happened?
Tell me!
Maybe...
Wu Ming will be no more.
What makes you say that?
Tian Yi set a trap at Black Duke Manor.
The sole purpose is
to completely eliminate Wu Ming.
The number you dialed is powered off.
Please try again later.
Don't waste your time.
Tian Yi's top fighters are all deployed,
along with elite underworld assassins.
There's no escape for Wu Ming.
Such a brilliant, extraordinary man.
What a shame.
If he'd been given more time,
no one would've been able to handle him.
Hello?
Noda Tomoko!
Wu Ming went to Black Duke Manor.
Yes.
He went alone.
You...
Why let him go to Black Duke Manor alone?
They've laid an inescapable trap there!
Take everyone to Black Duke Manor now!
I'll bring my people to save him too.
Are you trying to get yourselves killed?
Wu Ming once helped me.
I'm willing to risk everything for him.
Wu Ming gave us orders.
He just told us to hold the fort.
I suggest you don't make things worse.
Going there won't change anything.
Hello?
All you can do now
is wait for the outcome.
But you should brace yourself.
Not all miracles
actually happen.
So many people went in.
Can Brother Ming handle it?
Brother Ming said,
"No risk, no reward."
Rather than live in fear,
better to wipe them all out.
Slaughter them until the sky turns dark.
Once he slaughters them all,
no one will dare mess with us again.
And that bug hiding in the gutter
will finally surface.
But he's heavily outnumbered.
We must trust Brother Ming is invincible.
Trust Brother Ming.
I know you trust Brother Ming.
Then why did you bring all this stuff?
Better safe than sorry.
The fight's started!
Should we move the car farther away?
What are you waiting for?
You're actually worth our full force.
Your heart
must be quite delicious.
Boy,
These hammers weigh over 300 pounds.
Think you can take a hit?
Sis,
Are we really just doing nothing,
just waiting here?
You heard them just now.
Tian Yi's Four Death Gods,
Heaven Thunder, Earth Fire,
and top assassins who kill for money,
have all gone to Black Duke Manor.
That place is a meat grinder right now.
Wu Ming is strong, but he's only human.
He's not a god.
Think he can take on the world alone?
Even though he won't let us go,
we need to show our resolve.
Death before dishonor.
Gather all the forces of the Noda Family
to lend him a hand.
Understood.
Let this proud man see
the power we have.
The Noda Family has a long legacy.
We're no pushovers.
Where's Tian Yi?
Don't even think about it!
Where is he?
Pure Water Palace.
Wu Ming,
I'm willing to be your woman.
You're not worthy.
Another one with a death wish.
My husband sure is charming.
I'm not here to die.
I just came to take a look.
Qianqian,
Think this through carefully.
There's nothing to think about.
My mind is made up.
Wang Qianqian,
Your handful of men won't change a thing.
So what?
At worst, we die.
Attack!
How is that possible?
He actually fought his way out.
Tian Yi's four fierce generals...
those assassins...
are they all...
Honey,
Are you okay?
Wu Ming,
The four masters and top assassins...
where are they?
Dead.
Good riddance!
Honey,
You have no idea how worried we were.
Sis and I gathered all the family's men
to stand with you through life and death.
Thank goodness you're okay.
Brother Ming,
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
To Pure Water Palace.